<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project 3</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Project 3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python - REGEX</title>
      <link>/blog/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/python/</guid>
      <description>REGEX When being introduced to Python during the last unit this semester, I found the use of regular expressions, or REGEX for short, to be amazingly efficient in use of large sets of data. I definitely appreciated becoming proficient in R, but learning some Python basics seemed like a breath of fresh air.
During the second homework assignment was when I was really tested with my REGEX skills in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects       code{white-space: pre;} pre:not([class]) { background-color: white; }  if (window.hljs) { hljs.configure({languages: []}); hljs.initHighlightingOnLoad(); if (document.readyState &amp;&amp; document.readyState === &#34;complete&#34;) { window.setTimeout(function() { hljs.initHighlighting(); }, 0); } }  h1 { font-size: 34px; } h1.title { font-size: 38px; } h2 { font-size: 30px; } h3 { font-size: 24px; } h4 { font-size: 18px; } h5 { font-size: 16px; } h6 { font-size: 12px; } .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1 - Exploratory Data Analysis
  Project 2 - Modeling, Testing, and Predicting
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>0. Introduction I have chosen two datasets provided by the FiveThirtyEight package. The first dataset labeled bad_drivers lists data from all 50 U.S. states and the District of Columbia. The dataset contains several numerical variables on the number of drivers per state involved in fatal collisions per billion miles (num_drivers), the percentage of drivers involved in fatal collisions who were speeding (perc_speeding), the percentage of drivers involved in fatal collisions who were alcohol-impaired (perc_alcohol), the percentage of drivers involved in fatal collisions who were not distracted (perc_not_distracted), the percentage of drivers involved in fatal collisions who had not been involved in any previous accidents (perc_no_previous), car insurance premiums in U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>0. Introduction The dataset channing contains data on 462 seniors that, at some point in time, lived in the Channing House retirement home in Palo Alto, California. The data was collected from the opening of the house in 1964 until July 1, 1975. The sex variable accounts for the 97 men and 365 women that had passed through the retirement home. The entry variable accounts for each resident’s age (in months) upon entry to the home.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>